<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BookApp</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="Intorduction_ch">"Snow White" is a 19th-century German fairy tale that is today known widely across the Western world. The Brothers Grimm published it in 1812 in the first edition of their collection Grimms Fairy Tales, numbered as Tale 53.</string>
    <string name="Intorduction2_ch">"The original German title was Sneewittchen, a Low German form, but the first version gave the High German translation Schneeweißchen, and the tale has become known in German by the mixed form Schneewittchen. The Grimms completed their final revision of the story in 1854, which can be found in the in 1957 version of Grimms Fairy Tales.</string>
    <string name="ChOnePara1">"Once upon a time, in a kingdom very far away, there lived a king and a queen.
The king was handsome and kind. Everybody loved him. But the real ruler of the kingdom was his wife — the queen.
Before she became queen, she worked in the castle kitchen. She was very poor. But she was also very beautiful, and funny, and very good at Scrabble.
So the king fell in love with her, and married her."</string>
    <string name="ChOnePara2">"The king loved the queen very much. But the queen was always afraid that the king would meet someone more beautiful.
Luckily, the queen had a magic mirror. The mirror saw everything and knew everything.
Every day the queen looked at herself in the mirror, and asked: “Magic mirror on the wall, who is the most beautiful of all?”
And the mirror replied:
“You are, my Queen! You are the most beautiful woman in the whole world.”
The queen was happy. She knew there was nobody in the world as beautiful as her."</string>
    <string name="Ch2Para1">"The hunter found Snow White, and took her into the forest.
When they reached the deepest, darkest part of the forest, the hunter stopped. “Go!” he whispered. “Run fast and far and don't ever go home!”‍
Snow White watched the hunter disappear.
“Well, I can’t go home now,” she muttered. She looked around at the dark and silent forest. It started to rain.
“But I can’t stay here either. Ok feet, let’s go.” "</string>
    <string name="Ch2Para2">"Snow White ran and ran. She ran across a stream, up a hill, and down into a dark valley. She ran all morning.
By midday her pale skin and rosy cheeks were covered in mud and scratches.
By early afternoon her long black hair was full of sticks and leaves.
By night, she was not beautiful anymore. She was tired, hungry, and shivering with cold.
But then Snow White smelled woodsmoke in the air. She followed the smell and found a cottage in the woods. There was a warm, golden glow from the windows. She knocked on the door."</string>
    <string name="Ch3Para1">"Back at the castle, the queen was feeling better. She thought Snow White was gone forever. But she was still a little afraid.
“Come and play Scrabble with me, my love!” shouted the King from the bottom of the stairs. “You can go first!”
“Maybe later, dearest,” replied the queen. She stood in front of her magic mirror.
“Magic mirror on the wall, who is the most beautiful of all?”
"</string>
    <string name="Ch3Para2">"“She is living with the seven dwarfs in the forest,” said the mirror. “Last night, she was not very beautiful. But as of…  1pm today, she is more beautiful than you.”
“RATS!” shouted the queen. She went to her closet and got her old coat and old boots.
“I’ll have to kill her myself!”
She ran out of the palace,  jumped into her fastest carriage, and sped off towards the forest.Snow White was reading beside the fire when there was a knock on the door.
KNOCK KNOCK!
She peeked through the window. There was a woman holding a basket of fruit. The woman had a beautiful face, but she was wearing an old dress and old boots."</string>
    <string name="Ch4Para1">"When the dwarfs arrived home, they found Snow White lying on the floor.
They yelled in her ears. They tickled her feet. They poured cold water on her face. But she didn't wake up.
“Is she ... dead?” asked one dwarf.
“She doesn’t seem to be alive…” said a second.
And so the dwarfs made a glass coffin for their beloved friend.
They set it on a table in a beautiful part of the forest, surrounded by flowers."</string>
    <string name="Ch4Para2">"One day, a prince from a different kingdom was walking through the forest with his dog.
He saw Snow White’s strange glass coffin. He brushed off the leaves and saw Snow White inside.
Just then, he tripped over his dog and knocked the coffin off the table! Snow White rolled out of the coffin and onto the grass.
"</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>